♪〜
〜♪
（店内に流れる音楽）
Vash the Stampede?
（男Ａ）
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード？
（男Ｂ）ああ
Yeah. They say the man
with $ $60 billion on his head...
あの600億ダブドルの賞金首が—
ダンキンの田舎町に
現れたんだとよ
...showed up in Dankin Town.
Didn't you hear?
知らなかったのか？
（男Ａ）ふん！
…で どうなったんだ？
So, what happened?
（男Ｂ）
町が消えちまったんだとよ
They say the town got wasted!
Dankin was buried in corpses.
なんでも ダンキンじゃ
死体が山になってて—
The coffin maker got so rich, he
built himself a mansion made ofwood!
もうかりすぎた棺おけ屋が
木の御殿をおっ建てたらしいぜ
（口笛）
That's nuts!
（男Ａ）そいつはすげえや
What'd you expect?
（男Ｂ）当然よ
Messing with Vash
is like waltzing with Death.
ヴァッシュに
関わるってことは—
死に神と ワルツを
踊るってことと同じだ
He kills women and children,
and picks off any town he pleases.
女 子どもを平気で殺し
町を軽く消滅させる
"The Humanoid Typhoon"
is the perfect name for him!
まったく“ヒューマノイド･
タイフーン”とは—
よく言ったもんだぜ
（バーテン）ああっ！
（大きな物音）
（男Ａ）ああ？
（バーテン）あっ ああ…
うわあ！
（金属音）
（２人）ああ？
（不気味な音）
（デカルト）ふん！
（空を切る音）
（客Ｂ）うっ！
（客Ａ）ああ…
（衝撃音）
What the f?!
な… 何だ？
（２人）ヒ… ヒャー
（発砲音）
（地響き）
（一同）うっ…
（ブーメランが空を切る音）
（デカルト）フーフフフ
ようやく見つけたぜ
I finally found you.
（発砲音）
One night, and look at this.
（保安官）一晩でこれだ
I didn't believe the rumors,
but he really is a typhoon.
うわさにゃ聞いてたが
やつは台風そのものだよ
Over half the town is rubble!
町が半分も壊されちまった
（ルーズ･ルース）
そいつは災難だったなあ
That's a real shame.
At least he made the undertakers happy.
What did he get, 100? 200?
だが 葬儀屋は
うれしがってるだろ
100か？ 200か？
（保安官）それがゼロなんだ
Actually, zero.
Countless people were injured,
but there were no fatalities.
ケガ人は
数えられねえ程出たが—
死者は出ていない
I guess you don't need God
for a miracle.
神様がいなくても
奇跡は起こるってことだ
What did he look like?
（ルース）どんなやつだった？
ハア…
He's a short-legged,
earringed giant in red.
赤い服を着てイヤリングをした
短足の大男だそうだ
I didn't get a look at him myself.
保安官のわしも
確認してはいないがな
Thanks.
（ルース）ありがとよ
Whateveryou do, stay away
from him! Foryour own good.
（保安官）
間違っても手え出すな
こりゃ忠告だ
Red...
（ルース）赤い服…
The area of Dankin
is nearly demolished.
（ラジオの音声）
ダンキン地方は
ほぼ壊滅
All residents, please go to
your designated shelter areas.
住民の皆さんは—
所定の避難場所へ
集合してください
The next update will be at 1.30 pm.
次回の放送は…
（ドアベルの音）
（一同）ん？
Please enjoy our musical selection.
（ドアの閉まる音）
（客たち）ヘッヘッヘッヘッ
What'll it be?
（バーのマスター）注文は？
（メリル･ストライフ）
バナナサンデー
A banana sundae.
ああ？
A gâteau mille-feuille
with Ceylon tea!
（ミリィ･トンプソン）
ガトーミルフィーユと
セイロンティーのセット
（客たち）でやーっ
（客Ａ）やあーっ
Listen missies, the gag won't
work unless you order milk!
お嬢ちゃんたちよお
そういうギャグは—
〝ミルク〞で行くのが
お約束だろうが！
Then we'd give you
all the milk you want!
（客Ｂ）
そうすりゃ 俺たちがたっぷり
ごちそうしてやるってえのに
Although it wouldn't be free.
（客Ｃ）もちろん代金は
しっかりと頂くがな
（客たち）アハハハハ
But I don't want milk,
I want Ceylon tea.
ミルクじゃなくて—
セイロンティーって
言ったんですよ
ああーっ
（客Ｂ）ああ…
（客Ｃ）おい
Hey!
I'm so sorry!
あっ ごめんなさーい
You clumsy bitch!
コラ この女(あま)！
うん…
あっ またスリング
切れちゃいましたあ
I broke another sling.
You have a spare, don't you?
Be more careful.
（メリル）
予備はありますわね
気をつけてください
（ミリィ）はい
I will!
な… 何だ あいつ
- What is she?!
- A monster!
怪力女
By the way, mister, we heard that
Vash the Stampede was in Felnarl...
ところでマスター
フェルナールの町に—
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードが
現れたって聞いたんですけど
Vash? Who are you two?
ヴァッシュ？
…って 何だ あんたら
Are you innocent-looking things
after the $ $60 billion reward?
カワイイ顔して—
600億ダブドルの賞金首
狙ってんのかい？
違いますわ
Not at all.
We're here on business.
私たち お仕事で来たんです
Business?
仕事…
Well, I didn't see him myself...
まあ 俺は
直接見たわけじゃねえが—
...but they say he
left town before dawn.
明け方ごろに町から
いなくなったらしい
東のほうに向かったって話だ
They say he went east.
Can you tell us
what he looks like?
どんな人物か分かります？
うん？ ああ…
He stands about 12 feel tall
and wields a huge weapon.
身の丈12フィールぐらいで—
巨大な武器を振り回すらしい
（客たち）ひいっ！
（バーのマスター）それと—
And he's supposed
to have a Mohawk.
モヒカン刈りの男って聞いたな
He has tons ofhenchmen...
手下の数も かなりいて—
...and is the worst kind
ofwomanizer out there.
女癖は最低を通り越して
最悪だそうだ
Ma'am!
先輩
A man with a huge
weapon and a Mohawk.
巨大な武器を持つ
モヒカン刈りの男
That's him, all right!
間違いありませんわ
Where'd he go?
野郎 どこ行きやがった
Find him, even ifyou have
to dig up the entire area!
ここら辺を 丸ごと
掘り返してでも捜しだせ
But, boss, you think that
yellow coward was really him?
（手下Ａ）しかし 頭(かしら)
あの腰抜けが本当にそうなんすか？
I can't believe it.
Let's move on.
あっしには
信じられませんぜ
ほかを当たったほうが…
ああっ！
You're real big
to give me orders.
俺に意見するとは
お前も出世したな
（手下Ａ）うう…
You saw what he was wearing!
Get him!
やつの格好を見たろ？
必ずしとめるんだ
Get him or I'll break your neck!
でなきゃ 俺が
お前の息を止めるぞ
Yes, boss!
（手下Ａ）ヘ… へい
（デカルト）ああ？
（手下Ｂ）ギャー　うっ…
（ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード）
ぶはーっ！
I thought I'd suffocate.
酸欠で死ぬかと思ったあ
You!!
（手下Ｂ）貴様！
（ヴァッシュ）ぷいっ
Pardon me, won't you?
（ヴァッシュ）はーい
ちょっくらごめんなさいよ
Thanks to you guys...
しかし まいったねえ
おかげで…
（空撃ちする音）
（手下たち）エヘヘッ
だあーっ
ウハハハハッ
（発砲音）
（ヴァッシュ）あっ あっ あっ
...I almost went to pieces.
…っていう
危機的状況だったからな
はっ 脱出できただけでも
ミラクル ミラクル
It's a miracle I got away.
I found him!
He's over there!!
（手下Ｃ）
いたぞ！ あそこだ
ノオッ！
（手下Ｃ）がっ
Perfect!
（ヴァッシュ）決まった！
（発砲音）
うああ！ アハハ
（デカルト）
ふん　ふさけやがって
He thinks he's funny.
Hunt him down.
（デカルト）追い込むぞ
（手下Ａ）へい
（ヴァッシュ）ハッ ハッ ハッ…
ハアッ ハアッ
腹 減った…
I'm hungry.
Persistent, aren't they?
しつこいねえ
Ha ha ha! I'm like
a standing target over here!
（ヴァッシュ）ワーッハッハ
こんな所に立っている私は
格好の的(まと)だ
（手下Ｄ）こっちだ！
うおお…
う… うう！
（発砲音）
You...
こいつ
Don't move now!
I've got you in my sights!
はーい 動かないでね
狙ってますよ 狙ってますよ
Boss, he's over here!!
頭！ 野郎は ここにいまっせ
Er, I'd ratheryou
lowered the gun quietly.
あの 黙って銃を
下ろしてほしいんですけど…
Forget it!
断る
Surely you don't like pain?
痛いの嫌いでしょ？
I'm used to it.
慣れてる
Your little wife
and kids are crying.
田舎の奥さんや子どもが
泣いてますよ
I'm single, and no girl
has ever looked my way.
俺は独身で—
生まれてから こっち
女にモテたことはねえ
What a lonely life!
さみしい人生だなあ
Like I'm saying...
だからよお
...die. For our happiness.
死んでくれよ
俺たちの幸せのために
“はい”って言えないですよ
I can't do that.
（空(くう)を切る音）
（ヴァッシュ）伏せろ！
Get down!
（手下Ｄ）どあっ！
（衝撃音）
チッ！
（足音）
ううっ か… 頭あ…
B-Boss!
フフフフフ
Well done. I commend you.
よくやった　褒めてやる
You hurt your pal, too.
Where's the justice in that?
（ヴァッシュ）
仲間を巻き添えにして—
- The pain...
You hurt your pal, too.
Where's the justice in that?
あんたの正義は
何も言わないのか？
We are not pals,
we are partners in fate!
仲間じゃねえ 運命共同体だ
My happiness
is his happiness!
俺の幸せが
やつの幸せになる
That's so beautiful.
ステキなお言葉だ
So go ahead and shoot me...
何なら 撃っても
かまわねえんだぜ
...if that big gun ofyours
isn't just for show.
その ゴツい銃が
飾り物(もん)じゃなければな
I can't stand blood.
The sight ofit makes me faint!
僕 血が苦手なの
見ただけで
気い失っちゃうんだ
Okay, then! Let's see what happens
when you see your own blood!
そうかい
じゃあ 自分の血を見て
どうなるか実験タイムだ
うう…
You! Hold him down
for my happiness!
（デカルト）
おい 俺の幸せのために
やつを取り押さえろ！
（手下Ｄ）ギャアー！
ぐあーっ
（手下Ｄ）うう…
（ヴァッシュ）ああ…
（デカルト）
どうだい とても献身的だろ
See how devoted he is?
Ow, ow!
いーてててて
Could you be more gentle?
もうちょっと優しく
お願いしますよお
（トマの鳴き声）
Good. Now to take him in to the Feds.
よーし　あとは連邦保安局に
連れていくだけだ
デヘヘ
Ya-hoo! We'll be rich!
いやっほーっ
これで俺たちは大金持ちだ！
ハハハハッ
（２人）ん？
（トマの鳴き声）
Women? They friends ofhis?
女？ 仲間ですかね？
（デカルト）ああ？
獲物をかすめ取る気か？
Are they after our prize?
We're going in.
いくわよ
Yes, ma'am!
はい
What do you want?
何だ 貴様ら
は… 初めてお目に
かっ かかります
P-Pleased to m-meet you!
I'm Meryl Stryfe from
the Bernardelli Insurance Society.
わ… 私は
ベルナルデリ保険協会の—
メリル･ストライフと申します
I'm Milly Thompson!
ミリィ･トンプソンです
Please accept this
token of good will!
こ… これ
つまらない物ですけど
Smooth, ma'am!
ナイスです 先輩！
What're you doing here?
You with him?
何しに来た？
こいつの仲間か？
（ヴァッシュ）エヘッ
No! We're here on behalf of
the Bernardelli Insurance Society...
いえ 私たちは—
ベルナルデリ保険協会の
意向により ヴァッシュ…
...for Vash the...
（銃声）
（メリルとミリィ）ひいっ！
（デカルトたち）何だ？
What?!
（ルーズ･ルース）
フフフフッ やっと見つけたぜ
I finally found you,
my $ $60 billion beauty...
600億ダブドルの賞金首
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード
...Vash the Stampede.
んん！
（メリルとミリィ）ああ？
え？
I am Ruth Loose...
俺は“コンスタンツライフル”の
異名を取る賞金稼ぎ
...the bounty hunter
called "Constance Rifle."
ルーズ･ルース
Vash the Stampede,
I'm here foryour head.
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード
今から貴様の首を頂く
何だと！
What?!
- Ma'am!
- This is bad.
（ミリィ）先輩
（メリル）マズいですわ
I think I missed something.
じ… 事情が分かんないっす
It's a privilege to meet you,
Vash the Stampede.
会えてうれしいぜ
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード
Your head is starting
to resemble a greenback.
貴様の顔が
札束に見えてきたよ
なんたって その首には—
You can't blame me, since
it is worth $ $60 billion.
600億ダブドルの賞金が
懸かってるんだからな
What'll we do, ma'am?
（ミリィ）先輩 どうします？
T-That goes without saying!
We stop them!
き… 決まってますわ
止めるのよ
あ… あの…
Uh...
（デカルト）おい
（メリルとミリィ）ひいっ
Hey! You said
your name is Ruth?
てめえ ルースとか言ったな
Uh, listen!
（メリル）
あの 聞いてくださ…
I'm glad you enjoy your job,
but I think you're a little late.
仕事に精出すのは結構だが—
一足遅かったんじゃねえか？
（メリル）
ちょ… ちょっと聞いてく…
Please listen...
ふん 遅い？
Late? I don't think so.
そうでもないさ
うわっ！ バカ野郎
どこ狙っていやがる
You idiot! Where are you
pointing that thing?!
At a $ $60 billion skull.
（ルース）
600億ダブドルの脳天だ
Don't be a moron!
（デカルト）
勘違いするんじゃねえ！
（メリルとミリィ）へっ？
（手下Ａ）ヒヒヒ アハハハ
The boss, Vash?!
Where'd you get that idea?
頭がヴァッシュ？
そりゃ 何のデマだ？
（メリルとミリィ）え？
I'm not fool enough
to listen to no henchman.
手下の言うことなど
誰が信じるか
That's a mighty poor joke.
ジョークとしては
レベルが低いぜ
ケッ！ バカバカしい
This is ridiculous!
Quit wasting my time.
つきあってられねえ
さっさと…
Don't move!
（ルース）動くな！
（デカルト）うん？
Ashort-legged,
earringed giant in red.
赤い服を着て
イヤリングをしている短足の男
お前が
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードだ
You are Vash the Stampede!
何言ってやがる！
What are you talking about?!
Vash is a blonde man in a
red coat, with a big gun!
ヴァッシュは赤いコートを着て—
ゴツい銃を持った 金髪の男だ！
N-No, he isn't!
い… いえ
ヴァッシュは
大きな武器を持った—
Vash is a man with a
big weapon and a Mohawk!!
モヒカン刈りの男ですわよ
（ミリィ）何か変ですわね
That's strange.
The rumors don't match.
（メリル）
うわさがバラバラですわ
（ミリィ）どうします？
What now?
What now?! We have to
believe what we heard.
（メリル）“どうします”って—
うわさを信じるしか
ありませんわ
（ミリィ）でも…
But...
あっ…
At any rate, I'm not Vash!
とにかく 俺は
ヴァッシュじゃねえ
（手下Ａ）頭
（デカルト）ん？
Boss, look!
The Feds will pay $ $60 billion
for Vash the Stampede, dead or alive.
（ルース）
600億ダブドルの賞金は
生死に関わらず—
連邦政府から支払われる
I can kill you now,
ifyou like.
今すぐ仏にしてやっても
いいんだぜ
Blonde man, red coat, big gun.
金髪 デカい銃 赤い服…
フフフフフッ
I see. You're trying
to get the jump on me...
そうか
先手を打とうって腹か
ええ？ ヴァッシュさんよ
...Vash!
What?
何だと？
（メリルとミリィ）はあ？
You even came up with
a fake name! Nice plan!
（デカルト）
しかも偽名まで使うとは
手が込んでるじゃねえか
Huh?
（ミリィ）あ… あれ？
He's gotta be the real deal!
Let's get him!
野郎が本物に違えねえ
やるぜ！
ふん なるほど
I see. So that's how
you stayed alive.
そうやって
生き延びてきたのかい
（銃声）
Blast him!!
撃て 撃て
（発砲音）
（一同）うわあーっ！
（爆発音）
だあーっ
Bastard!
（デカルト）
野郎… 調子に乗りやがって！
Don't push your luck!
でやあーっ
（衝突音）
ああ…
ヒューマノイド･タイフーンが
暴れだしちゃいましたよ
The Humanoid Typhoon is loose!
What'll we do, ma'am?
どうします？ 先輩
What'll we do?! Naturally...
“どうします”って…
もちろん
逃げるに決まってますわ
...we run away!
While there's life, there's hope!
命あっての物種(ものだね)ですよね
（爆発音）
We have to give the town
an evacuation order, or else!
（メリル）
町に避難勧告を出さないと
大変なことになりますわよ
But, ma'am, isn't this
like abandoning our duty?
でも先輩 このままだと—
仕事を投げ出してしまうことに
なりませんか？
Well, yes, but ifwe
don't contact the town...
かといって
町に連絡しないのも…
Mm, these are really tasty!
（ヴァッシュ）
ああー うまい うまい
これ うまい
How did you get those?!
あっ あなた いつの間に
Thanks! I was getting hungry!
Danke, danke!
助かったよ おなかも膨れるし
ダンケ ダンケ
別に あなたを助けるために
やったことではありませんわ
We didn't come here
to save you, you know!
Then what were you doing there?
You go for guys like that?
だったら どうして
あんな所に来たんだい？
ああいう男が趣味なのかい？
I'm afraid you're wrong!
We came on business!
そうじゃありません！
私たちは仕事で来たんです
We're disaster investigators for
the Bernardelli Insurance Society!
私たちベルナルデリ保険協会の
災害調査員なんですよ
So why are insurance people
after a wanted man?
その保険屋さんがどうして
賞金首を追いかけるんだい？
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードに
よって 引き起こされた事件は—
There have been over 300
Vash the Stampede-related disasters.
300件を超えてますのよ
そのことで保険会社が
どういうリスクを負うかは—
You can understand what kind of
risk an insurance company takes.
分かりますわね
Yeah, that must be rough.
（ヴァッシュ）
なるほど 大変なんだ
チッ！ だからこそ私たちが
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードを—
That's why we're here to keep
him under 24-hour surveillance...
24時間監視して—
...to prevent further damage!
被害を抑制することになったんです
24-hour WHAT?!
に… 24時間！
（ミリィ）
どうしたんですか？
What's wrong?
- N-Nothing!
- I know!
い… いえ
（メリル）あっ そうだわ
In exchange for this and the donuts,
would you please go warn the town?
よろしければ
ドーナツとこれで—
町の人たちに避難するように
言ってあげてください
I'll even lend you a thomas.
トマを１頭 お貸ししますわ
You're going back there?
戻るつもりなのかい？
It's our job.
それが仕事ですから
ふん…
It looks like it's over.
（メリル）
終わったみたいですわね
Thank goodness
there was no damage.
被害もなくて何よりですわ
But didn't the
bounty hunter get killed?
（ミリィ）
でも あの賞金稼ぎの人
死んじゃったんでしょうね
Yes, it's sad.
（メリル）悲しいですけどね
So how are we going to
approach him this time?
（ミリィ）
…で 今度はどうやって
接触するつもりなんですか？
（メリル）フフッ
This one's a thirty-pack!
30個入りですわよ
Way to go, ma'am!
さすが先輩！
人間礼節を重んじれば
何も恐れることはなくってよ
lfyou are courteous,
there is nothing to fear.
（空を切る音）
（衝撃音）
（メリルとミリィ）キャーッ！
You've got a lot of nerve
to come back here!
（デカルト）お前ら
ノコノコ戻ってきたのか？
Uh, please accept this
token of good will!
（メリル）あ… あの
これ つまらない物ですが
Where's the guy who
ran away with you?
お前らと一緒に逃げた野郎は
どこにいる？
W-We split up halfway!
（ミリィ）
と… 途中で別れました
ふん！
苦労して追い詰めたのに
It was so damned hard
to track him down.
どうしてくれるんだ！
ルースさんよお
What did I ever do to you, Ruth?!
It's you!
（ミリィ）あなたは！
How are you alive?!
Weren't you fighting?
（メリル）
なんで 生きてるんです？
ケンカしてませんでした？
We each realized our mistakes.
双方の誤解が解けたのさ
Each?! You're the one
who screwed up!
何言ってやがる！
勝手に間違えたのは
てめえだろうが
いいか 分け前は
俺が７ お前が３だ
Now listen!
We split the pot 70/30!
Don't you forget it!
（デカルト）忘れんなよ
（ルース）ふん
What is this about?
どういうことですの？
- Okay, let's go!
- Just a moment.
よーし　行くぜ
（ルース）ちょっと待った
（縄がきしむ音）
Ma'am...
（ミリィ）せんぱーい
I knew we shouldn't
have taken this job.
やっぱり こんな仕事
受けなければよかったですわ
What good will this do?
（デカルト）こんなことして
何になるんだよ ええ？
Just enjoy.
（ルース）
いいから楽しんでくれ
（デカルト）
ふん　悪趣味だな
You have bad taste.
I kind oflike it.
しかし 俺も
こういうのが好みだ
The rumor did say he's
"the worst kind ofwomanizer."
うわさじゃ 女癖は最悪だって
Now is not the time
to remind me.
こんな時に
言うことじゃなくってよ
（足音）
（メリルとミリィ）ううっ！
（メリルとミリィ）ううっ…
ウヘヘヘヘ
Which will it be? Pleasure
before death, or just death?
楽しんでから死ぬのと
楽しまずに死ぬのと
どっちがいい？
ひいっ！
（メリル）ううっ…
ああ？
（ヴァッシュ）お頭 大変ですー！
Boss, it's an emergency!
What is it?!
何だ！
（ヴァッシュ）いやっ
大変なのは俺なんですー
I'm having an emergency!!
（デカルト）野郎！
（ルース）来た！
- Why that...
- He's here!
あの人
It's him!
（銃声）
キャー あーっ 痛い！
（ヴァッシュ）ギャオ！
（ルース）やった！
Got him!
ハーッ ていっ！
逃げろ！
Run!!
（発砲音）
わざわざ戻ってくるたあ
手間が省けたぜ
Thanks for saving me the trouble
oflooking foryou, Vash the Stampede!
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード！
Vash?
（メリル）ヴァッシュ…
（デカルト）たあっ！
おっ
He's gone! Where'd he go?!
いねえ　ど… どこだ？
Where are you going?
（ルース）お前 どこへ行く？
- To the potty, sir!
- Oh.
（男）ちょっとトイレへ
（ルース）そうか
（銃声）
（ヴァッシュ）だあっ！
（ヴァッシュ）
キャハッ…
He saved us, but...
（ミリィ）
助けてくれたけど
...he's embarrassing to watch.
（メリル）なんか
カッコ悪いですわね
んがあー 危ねえ
All right! Corner him!
しめた！ 追い込めるぞ
Uh-oh.
（ヴァッシュ）あらら…
That's far enough, Vash!
（デカルト）
そこまでだ ヴァッシュ
So, you wanna die by my boomerang,
or do a suicide dive off the cliff?
どうする
俺のブーメランで死ぬか？
それとも崖からダイブして
自殺するかあ？
Suicide?
（ヴァッシュ）自殺？
I disapprove of suicide
more than anything.
それは俺が一番嫌いな行為だ
ふん
Then the boomerang you get.
なら ブーメランの露だな
うーん
いやあああーっ！
はっ！
（ヴァッシュ）ふん！
What?!
（デカルト）なに？
（ヴァッシュ）ひよよよよっ！
（デカルト）うーん…
（ヴァッシュ）ふっ！
（ヴァッシュ）てへっ
It's only fun until
someone gets hurt!
こんな危ない物(もん)
使っちゃダメだよお
（リールが巻かれる音）
You!!
てめえ！
ああああっ
（体が締まる音）
（２人）頭！
Boss!
うわあ！
（デカルト）あっ…
（手下Ａ）頭がやられた
- He got the boss!
- He's not human!
（手下Ｅ）人間技じゃねえ
（手下たち）うわあーっ！
ハア… もろい信頼関係だ
Such fragile bonds of trust.
それと そこ！
And as foryou!
（ルース）ぬおっ！
Look out.
（ヴァッシュ）危ないですよ
Forwhat?!
な… 何を！
（衝突音）
（ルース）うわっ！
Oops, too late.
ちょっと遅かったかな
あっ ああっ ああ…
すまん　早くよくなってね
Sorry. Get well soon.
す… すごいわ
Amazing! He got both of them.
二人とも
やっつけてしまいましたわ
（ミリィ）まるで—
It's as ifhe were
Vash the Stampede!
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード
みたいですね
（メリル）えっ？
ドーナツと10ダブドル分は
働いたかな？
Did I work off
the donuts and the $ $10?
えっ？
ナーハハハハッ
（ヴァッシュの笑い声）
It couldn't be him.
あの人は違いますわ
（導火線の焼ける音）
（ヴァッシュ）ああーっ！
（爆発音）
（メリルとミリィ）うわーっ！
う… うわっ
あああああ…
（地響き）
（タイピングの音）
Disaster report.
（メリル）災害報告書
We have determined that the landslide
which destroyed Felnarl resulted...
フェルナールの町を壊滅させた
土砂崩れは—
ルーズ･ルースと名乗る男の—
... from illegal use of explosives
belonging to a man named Ruth Loose.
爆発物取締法違反によるものと判定
Please pay the insurance owed.
支払われる保険金は
規定通りでお願いします
ハア…
We're back to less
than zero on our Vash hunt.
結局 ヴァッシュ探しは
振り出しに戻るか…
And we can't ignore the rumors...
This is going to be difficult.
うわさを信じないわけに
いかないし
難しいですわねえ
あの人はどうなんですか？
What about him?
（メリル）ふん
That couldn't possibly be him.
あれは いくらなんでも
違いますわよ
そうですか…
Really?
（町の男Ａ）
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード？
Vash the Stampede?
（町の男Ｂ）ああ
Yeah, they say the man
with $ $60 billion on his head...
あの600億ダブドルの賞金首が—
...showed up in Felnarl.
フェルナールの町に
現れたんだとよ
- Didn't you hear?
- Nope. So, what happened?
お前 知らなかったのか？
（町の男Ａ）ああ
…で どうなったんだ？
（町の男Ｂ）
町がなくなったんだと
The town is gone.
だけどよ 死人は一人も
出なかったって話だぜ
Funny thing is,
they say nobody died.
（町の男Ａ）へえー
You mean like, you don't
need God for a miracle?
神様はいなくても
奇跡は起こるってか
（町の男Ａ･Ｂ）アハハハ
♪〜
〜♪
（ヴァッシュ）言葉では
伝えられないものがある
There is something which
cannot be expressed in words.
それは人の思いだ
People's emotions.
Emotions of the heart
cannot be defined.
心の中の思いは
言霊に宿らない
But there is one way
to read the emotions.
だが 思いを知るすべが
１つだけある
相手の目を見つめることだ
Look into their eyes.
The girl lied to me.
The gentleman lied to me.
少女は俺にウソをついた
紳士は俺にウソをついた
But the moment
I looked into their eyes...
だが 彼らの瞳を見た瞬間—
...fate began to alter,
to reveal the truth.
運命が流転し
真実が解き明かされていく
Just look into their eyes.
There is only one truth.
相手の目を見れば分かる
真実は１つしかない